sunwing.ca 2019-09-25

# Privacy Policy

Except with your consent, we will not transfer or assign in any form your Personal Information to or with third parties.  From time to time, we may disclose your Personal Information as set out below. We would always make that disclosure as permitted by law. When you agree to this Privacy Policy, you are, to the extent permitted by law, granting your consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to third parties for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy and to the extent stated in this section and as described in Section 3 above.  Circumstances where we might make such disclosure (in addition to those described in Section 3 above) include:

**Our affiliates and subsidiaries**

Sunwing may disclose and you authorize Sunwing to disclose your Personal Information with its affiliates and subsidiaries. 

**Our agents, service providers and suppliers**

Sunwing may share Personal Information with third parties engaged in providing services to you, or to carry out one or more of the purposes described above. These service providers are prohibited from using your Personal Information for any purpose other than to provide this assistance and are required to protect Personal Information collected by them or disclosed to them by Sunwing and to comply with the general privacy principles described in this Privacy Policy. These third parties may not process or otherwise use your Personal Information, except in accordance with Sunwing's Privacy Policy and as permitted by law.

**Legal requirements**

Sunwing reserves the right to disclose Personal Information to a third party if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order legally requires or authorizes us to do so or in the context of discovery procedures or if we determine it is necessary or desirable to comply with the law or to protect or defend our rights or property. We also reserve the right to retain Personal Information collected and to process such Personal Information to comply with accounting and tax rules and regulations and any specific record retention laws.

**Business transfers**

Sunwing also reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer Personal Information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale (including a liquidation, realization, foreclosure or repossession), lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or any portion of Sunwing or of any of the business or assets or shares of Sunwing or a division thereof in order for you to continue to receive the same products and services from the third party to the extent permitted by law and you consent to such disclosure and/or transfer.
